CHRISTIAN EZE

CONTACT

Email:

Christianlightgentry@gmail.com

Github:

https://github.com/xtianmedia

Contact Address:

Plot 11 Road4 Agip Estate, Ruemueme, Port-Harcourt, Nigeria.

Phone:

(+234) 906-7460-198

Website:

https://xtianmedia.netlify.app

EDUCATION:

Wisdom International Leadership
Institute, (WILI).
Agip Port Harcourt.
Basic Certificate Course.
2018

TRAINING

Harvoxx Tech Hub Front-End Web Development 2021

CERTIFICATIONS

Complete Html5, Css3 and JavaScript from Zero to expert.

Build Responsive Website like a Pro using Bootstrap5.

Professional Summary

A proficient and dexterous Front-end developer and digital media specialist based in Port-Harcourt, Nigeria.

Highly dynamic in tasks accomplishment with a fascination for creativity and visuals, he has successfully built well-structured websites with appealing UI for businesses and organizations at large.

Professional Experience

Front-End Developer Intern - Harvoxx Tech Hub 2022

- Created a responsive landing page using Html5, Css3.
 (https://projecthubhq.netlify.app)
- Cloned a multi section website using html5, css3, and JavaScript. (https://lanearkclone.netlify.app)
- Created a single page website with Css3, Html5 and JavaScript (https://buildwithharvoxxproject.netlify.app)
- Completed frontend challenge on different scope and site using Css3, Html5.

(https://fourcardsectionproject.netlify.app)

 built a multi section website for myself using Html5, Css3 and JavaScript; (https://xtianmedia.netlify.app)

Technical Skills

- HTML5 Css3 JavaScript
- Bootstrap Responsive Web Design
- Testing/Debugging Web Performance
- WordPress

Soft Skills

- Effective communication Problem Solving
- Analytical thinking Time Management Team Collaboration

Interests

- Full stack development
- Back-End technologies
- Php Jquery Python JavaScript

REFERENCES

Will be made available on request.



EDUCATION

Basic Certificate Course (BCC)

Wisdom International Leadership Institute, (WILI) 2018.

Senior Secondary School Certificate Examination (SSCE) Community Senior Secondary School, 2017.

CONTACT

PHONE

(+234) 906-7460-198

EMAIL

Christianlightgentry@gmail.com

WEBSITE

https://xtianmedia.netlify.app

ADDRESS

Agip Estate, Mile 4, Rumueme,
Port Harcourt, Nigeria.

REFERENCE

Will be made available on request.

CHRISTIAN EZE

DIGITAL MEDIA SPECIALIST

ABOUT ME

A proficient and dexterous digital media specialist based in Port-Harcourt, Nigeria.

He is the creative director of xtianmedia, a brand that incorporates all his skills and expertise.

He specializes on Creative Video Editing, Live Video Streaming/Virtual Set Up, Graphic designs, Web Designs and Social media management.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2018 - Present Live Video Streamer

Wisdom Power Christian Centre

In- charge of broadcasting online live videos & prerecorded, with well relatable software.

2020 - Present Media Manager

Wisdom Power Christian Centre

Strategize media workflow with the eye to see through media processes making sure there's no technical

disruption

2019 - Present Creative Director

Xtianmedia

Designed flyers, logos, banners using a well-defined

Info graphics.

Edit videos and motion graphics suitable for brand

voices.

SOFT SKILLS

He is a life-long learner with great communication skills, a team player and a problem solver, highly proficient in time management skills with an eminent attitude for results.

SOFTWARE SKILLS

Adobe Photoshop - Adobe Premiere Pro - Adobe illustrator

Microsoft Word - Microsoft PowerPoint - Adobe illustrator

OBS Studio - Vmix